Wow, I want them all! So cute!
Oh, no! Oh, wait a minute!
Oh my gosh! This is what I've always wanted to do!
Hey everyone! I'm Rina Matsuda!
Yes, let me tell you where I'm here today...
Ta-da!
I'm here at a PC store in Akihabara!
Yay!
I think it would be better to play on PS5 or something, since I'm a beginner.
But I really wanted to play on a gaming PC.
I've already decided to buy one.
Today, my dream is finally coming true!
Yay!
I've been interested in games since about a year ago.
I've been watching a lot of people's video games.
I still love it and watch it all the time!
I belong to this Crazy Raccoon.
I worked really hard to get this one, too.
Look at this!
Ta-da!
It's DARUMA is GOD!
I also have another one of Mr. Arisaka's.
That's when I started looking at various games.
I also used to like them.
I've been wanting to play games for a while now, and I'm getting stronger and stronger.
Today, I'd like to get a set of them with my own money.
I'm going to enjoy it!
Good evening.Good evening.
Good evening.
A gaming PC is what we call a gaming PC, right?
Yes, that's right, a gaming PC.
I'd like to try FPS.
Yes, I would like to.
For example, Epics.
Epics and Baroland.
I'd like to try it.
You have laptops here.
I didn't have much of an image of it.
I didn't have an image of a laptop computer, but I'd like to play games on it, too.
Of course, it's movable.
That's very nice.
It's compact.
Yes, recently, very high performance models have come out, so of course you can enjoy playing games on them.
Of course, you can enjoy playing games with this kind of model as well.
If you're an expert, you can make it yourself, right?
You can choose and purchase individual parts.
If you want to choose a case, we can make a custom-made model together with you.
Wow, I'd like to get to that level too!
By all means.
Yes, thank you very much. Wow, wow, wow... I'd like to make it a little easier to understand. Yes, I am a little conscious of distribution. Yes, I am a little conscious of the distribution. I'm really longing for something like this.
There are so many! Wow! Wow! Wow! I want to have it all!
Let's start with the keyboard.
Wow, keyboards are definitely important!
Do you have any recommendations? Do you have any recommendations?
Yes, nowadays, mechanical keyboards are very popular.
Yes, they are very popular.
There are many types of mechanical keyboards.
Certainly, there are already a lot of them.
Yes, there are some that make a clicking sound.
This bottom one is the quiet one.
Oh, it doesn't click at all.
Even if you press it very hard, it doesn't make a sound at all.
Well, it certainly doesn't make a sound.
It doesn't make a sound, but it's comfortable to press.
This area seems to be ticklish.
Yes, I think it feels a little different to the touch.
Wow, I definitely want to ring it.
You want to ring it? I see.
I want to ring it.
What's wrong? I was just going to say...
The green axis or the blue axis is the type that makes a sound.
Wow, it makes so much noise that it sounds like it's making a sound.
Yes, it has what is called a clicking sound.
Do you have more on this side?
Yes, we have a lot of them.
Wow, it glows in a really cool way.
Yes, it is.
Very cool.
Have you seen this? This series?
Yes, the Steve series. Yes, the Steve series.
I've seen some people introduced to it or something.
It's very popular.
Yes, so I'm thinking maybe I should start with that.
You can actually try it out for yourself.
Is that okay?
If that's okay with you?
I'd like to try it.
Yes, I would.
It's my first time. It's my first time to play this key mau.
But I understand that one.
Here, here, and here, right?
Yes, that's right. It's a fashionable game.
Here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here.
W, A, S, D.
That's right. It's here, isn't it?
Yes, you can move forward with W.
So this is what you mean when you say the mouse moves the viewpoint.
That's right. You can move the viewpoint with the mouse.
You can just hold down "W" to move forward.
How does it run? It's hard.
Shift. It may be difficult to press the pinky finger.
This one? It's hard. Running.
That's right. If you press the control as it is, it's sliding.
If you make your fingers fall down.
Here.
Shift and control while pressing the front. Shift and control while pushing the front.
That's it. You've got it. I'm sliding now.
It's very difficult. I'm moving my fingers like the moon.
Do you all do this?
Yes, they do.
It's very hard. I don't use my little finger very often.
It's amazing. What should we do?
The rest of the weapons are down.
You can choose the one you like.
It's hard. It's hard. This is the best.
How do you use it?
It's good.
Which finger do you use to press this? Index finger?
Yes, that's right.
Got it.
The bullet is on the left side.
This one?
It's good, isn't it?
Too good.
It's not so easy to get used to a keyboard mouse.
Yes, it is.
So, here we go.
This is it.
You can type with this.
How do you look through it?
Scope. Scope.
Right click.
It's hard.
Also, you can jump with the space button.
A little.
You must be really good. I'm a beginner.
Please look at me kindly.
It's my first time.
By the way, what axis is this?
This one has a blue axis.
Is that it? You mean the one that makes a sound, right?
It's cool. It's ticking.
See?
It's cool.
I'm tick-tocking.
I'm going to hit it while running.
I'm not running.
I'm going to go for a little bit, even though it's really my first time and I'm not used to anything yet.
Great. I'll be right here.
Wait a minute. Jump.
Jump in the space.
This is a door. That's not a door. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Detection.
Wait a minute.
I made a mistake.
Oh, no. Something's wrong. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Please.
Wait a minute. No weapons.
Really no weapons.
No weapons.
It's so big. I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Sorry.
It's hot. Sorry.
How was the experience?
It was a lot of fun.
It was mind-bogglingly difficult.
At first, yes. I think it is difficult when you use a keyboard and mouse.
Once you get used to it, on the contrary, it is often easier to play this way.
Everyone is like, "I'm using a gaming PC. For those of you who are using a gaming PC, how long did it take you to get used to it? How long did it take you to do it?
I'd like to know.
Please write everything in the comments section.
I'll really look at it, it's messed up.
I'm always looking at the YouTube comments section.
So if you have any suggestions, please write them down.
If you have any recommendations, please post them there.
I'll always go to see them in order of newest to oldest. Please do.
I would like to ask you to choose a lot of mice.
Certainly. This one, too.
Yes, I see. There are many.
Even more buttons than before.
All of these?All of these?
They are all Han buttons.
I can't push all these buttons.
You can do whatever you want.
Allocate them?
Yes. You can assign functions to your hand.
The most important thing is whether it fits your hand or not.
Yes, that is true. But is this the one you just saw?
The one you just saw is this one, isn't it?
This one?
It's a lighter type.
That's for sure. It is light.
Even professionals use it. It is a mouse that is used by a great number of professionals.
I would buy one in a heartbeat if I were told it was used by professionals.
There was a white one earlier, wasn't there?
That's right. We have four colors here.
Four colors?
It's a little hard to tell, but they are red and pink.
Cute.
Can I see the keyboard one more time?
Yes, you can. It's okay.
I'm sorry for looking at it in a normal way.
I think you can match the white mouse with the white keyboard.
It's cute. I want it to make a sound.
I'm going to go up to the PR department.
This way?
Then I've decided. I really decided.
I was really worried about it, I was really struggling with it,
To begin with, I was wondering what the theme of the room would be, black or white,
But white is still cute.
The PC I'm thinking of buying is red and black,
I was wondering what the theme of the room would be,
It doesn't really click, but it does make a clicking sound,
It doesn't click like crazy, but it makes a clicking sound,
Can you hear it?
This one.
I'll go with this one.
It's cute.
It glows and it's white.
It's pretty. Yay.
I've already decided on the mouse. It's early.
Here is the mouse.
This one is white.
I think I experienced it earlier,
I don't have anything to compare it to, so I don't really know that much,
I thought it was nice,
So I would like to choose this one.
I think I would like to match it with the white one.
Next, I would like to move on to the main body.
First of all, this is my item that you are looking for.
Take a look, everyone.
Ta-da!
It's a collaboration between Crazy Luckn and Galleria.
Just the CR shirt.
I see. I see.
I worked hard to get the shirt I collaborated with Bolt Room on.
It really has two footprints.
Crazy Luckn also has one type of exterior,
There are various types out there depending on the performance of the inside.
They are different. The highest specs are priced at...,
Oh, 530,000 yen?
532,980 yen.
That's a very good price.
It is very expensive,
First of all, here is the CPU.
It is an Intel Core i7-13700, which is a very high performance CPU,
Do you do any video editing?
I have never done so, but I think it would be useful if I could.
The CPU is also very suitable for this purpose.
The other part is what is called memory.
It is often compared to the size of a table or desk,
I would like to distribute games while playing games in the future.
It may be a long time in the future.
I'll pull it down here.
We'll lower the size.
If 32GB is set in advance, there are some recent games that use at least 12GB,
So, if you have 32GB, you can use it with a lot of leeway when you want to distribute your games.
So, I'm going to use this one.
I'm going to choose this one.
I've been looking at it for a while now.
I've been looking at it for a while, and I thought it looked really cool.
The keyboard is really white. The keyboard and stuff is really white.
It's nice, isn't it?
I guess that's part of it.
Let's do it.
So I finished buying all kinds of things,
I was so worried about it that the store was about to close,
I had a lot of time to think about it,
I bought that PC from the Crazy Luck collaboration!
I asked for delivery, so I only have this document this time,
I'm really looking forward to receiving it,
I'm really looking forward to receiving it, and I'm sure there are a lot of people who know a lot more about this than I do,
I'm really looking forward to receiving it, and I'm sure there are a lot of people who know more about this than I do,
I would be very happy if you could give me some advice in the comments section,
I would be very happy if you could give me a lot of advice in the comments section.
I hope to be able to stream games with you all on YouTube someday,
I'd like to expand my horizons with this new gaming PC I bought.
So, thank you all for watching the video so far.
If you think I'm going to get better at gaming, please click the "Good" button and give me a high rating.
Also, please subscribe to my channel.
See you soon.
Subtitle by Yuka